[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She will ____ reduce her chances of success if she continues to drink so much.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ its reluctance to advising parents how to bring up their children.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When faculty members assign an Incomplete grade they must ____ the work required.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his ____ to retire at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a particular way to the passage of time.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This review found that some guidelines and standards for reprocessing rigid laryngoscopes are incomplete, inadequate, and not ____ with one another.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "An ____ of this war is the rise of a large anti-war movement in the US.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She finds it ____ impossible to sit still in class.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How can educators design ____ to maximize the learning of all students?", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He reminds us that ____ teaching methods are part of coming of age in the world of the Japanese performing arts.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He both provided a message service and the ____ needed to send and receive wireless messages.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unfortunately, many drug users ____ from prison only to find themselves back there a few months later. This is because they cannot find or keep a job, and need to steal to finance their drug-taking habits.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The committee was asked to ____ a report listing the reasons in favour of invading Iraq.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein among the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not ____ much space.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He certainly could not ____ the existence of major problems.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can ____ sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "suffer", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Why do some children seem willing to ____ while others do not?", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "cooperate", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Such activity cannot be considered an adequate ____ for excellence in teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If mobile phones ____ any further, the keys will be too small to use.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam depend very heavily on ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company had to ____ their profit predictions after the cost of oil doubled within 6 months.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The manager used the occasion of the opening of the new factory ____ to make a speech about future developments.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Food irradiation can be an important ____ in the war against illness and death from foodborne diseases.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most economists believe that oil is the most important ____ in today's world.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "On December 4, 1955, the ____ decision was made to boycott the bus system until they were treated with courtesy and black drivers could be hired.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Scientists have not been able to ____ that the fossil is in fact that of a dinosaur.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The former is preferable for a ____ of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is suitable for ____s that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We should ____ the error of assuming that we will ever be able to comprehend the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The house was built so carelessly that it began to fall ____ after only a couple of years.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ language of the school is English but many documents are also translated into German.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's ____ rigid hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You have received this e-mail in the ____ belief that its contents would be of interest to you.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The union was not able to ____ all of its goals in this budget session.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not easy to represent an abstract idea in picture ____ so that ESL students can understand it.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The causes of gun and knife crime ____ young people is an important field of inquiry.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an ____ number will always yield an even number.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was characteristic of him to fail to ____ properly for the test.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Another reason to ____ student e-mail and internet usage is to ensure their safety.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to ____ herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to command serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most governments ____ to negotiate with kidnappers.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you currently do not possess the ____ to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of examinations leads some young people to commit suicide.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the information, we will make ____ efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Since the human body is not an ____ that can be disposed of at will, the results of research should be made available to the whole scientific community.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You have written a very clear and ____ report. Well done!", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He has a strong bias ____ religion since suffering badly as a child in a strictly religious school.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He has a strong bias ____ religion since suffering badly as a child in a strictly religious school.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The most serious objection raised against the ____ questions the use of self-report scales to assess prejudice.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the ____ damaged the atmosphere for the upcoming talks on practical matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The construction of the Interstate Highway System ran into serious financial problems because Congress did not ____ the cost of inflation.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We should never praise or ____ any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ how the government can hope to win the forthcoming election.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you are interested in checking out any of the books in the ____ case, please inquire at Circulation.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but ____ language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A ____ error in editing is to fix a word or phrase at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government needs to overcome its ____ to advising parents how to bring up their children.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company was in a very strong condition after winning a million dollar ____ to build its machines.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ response of the Hu Jintao government has won widespread praise, both inside and outside China.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is very ____ for a student to learn English so quickly. But she has!", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ head of police criticized the government's changes in drugs policy.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "former", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As migration is a spatial ____ process, it is important to comprehend how migrants perceive space and choose a destination in the space.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ the sports field so that games can be played after dark.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is the room where we store the science ____ ready for use in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The more information a sentence carries, the more it needs an ____ pattern that the reader can follow.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We have never in history needed to ____ of so much waste as we do today.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Lack of financial aid is a significant ____ on the chances of success in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse ____ of education and research institutions vested in the common goal of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most simply, the strength of a ____ is measured by determining how much energy is required to break the ____.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many British citizens and their ____ and military leaders were suspicious of Napoleon's motives and would not cooperate, so the tunnel project was abandoned.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Luckily, ____ to total coincidence, the men's and women's basketball teams started most of their games on the road.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Rules do not usually ____ creativity or passion; rather they demand conformity and make us fear change.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I'm in a ____ with John's parents. They want me to give him more homework, but I know he won't do it.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of this tutorial is to give you an idea of the sequence of events leading up to graduation.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Educational research is a useful tool for both ____ and theoretical problem solving.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A very effective way to check how the use of an English word is to look in Google for pages that ____ it.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The western end of the ____ route appears to have developed earlier than the eastern end, principally because of the development of the empires in the west.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is important to ____ that the information noted on the sign-off form is correct and that all necessary signatures have been obtained.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Would you help me with my science homework? - OK, but I'd ____ go out and play basketball.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his intention to ____ at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If your exam is closed book, you will want to ____ an outline that will assist you in studying until the day of the exam.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a ____ problem they would like to address and collaborate with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Board of Trustees met in April 2006 to discuss this report, and decided to ____ the construction of a 500 kW turbine.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The teacher was asked to ____ after it was discovered that he had lied about his absence from school.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not ____ with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Institute itself was an ____ separate from the Chemistry department.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We had disagreed strongly over politics before, and while these arguments did not ____ our friendship in the least, I wished to avoid potential conflict.", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "strain", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is a highly ____ view of the symbolic nature of physical reality.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new law will ____ unmarried mothers.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The text should contain a ____ description of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ response of the Hu Jintao government has won widespread praise, both inside and outside China.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher should vary presentation styles and take into ____ diverse abilities and interests.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the information, we will make ____ efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "average", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "ordinary, typical"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "So far scientists have been unable to ____ in their efforts to find a cure for cancer.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a very clear ____ in the school for expelling students who do not follow the rules.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many students now ____ an electronic dictionary.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Sufficient progress has been made with regard to drinking water to place within reach the target of halving the proportion of the population without ____ to safe drinking water between 1990 and 2015.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a minor consideration in the ____ decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Euro has taken on a dimension far greater than its ____ substance.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When two atoms of hydrogen ____ with one of oxygen, then the result is H2O, water.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These results indicate that ____ numbers of students attending the school are not attaining minimum levels of literacy and mathematical competency.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "short"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He has lost the ____ of being himself. Immigration laws have required him to pretend to be somebody else.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you ____ your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its structure or content.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "No wonder your computer doesn't work. You must ____ it to the monitor!", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This could substantially change the nature of the Internet we have come to know, to the ____ of both the consumers and the providers of information.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, besides not appearing as ____ entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most people are shocked by the ____ of life in Iraq since the invasion a few years ago.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost ____ presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The union leaders promised to ____ for a longer lunch break for the employees.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the experiment with a ____ excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can ____ sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The business tried to ____ its employees to work harder by offering an extra day's holiday to the best salesperson.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Individual academies apply the curriculum in the manner that best fits local ____ and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Such web content does not necessarily ____ the opinions of the University administration.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She found that the document had no ____ and conflicted with the assessments of military intelligence.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The drive to excel must be ____ in the culture of a university.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We can only ____ that Fulton was already too deeply committed to his own plan to consider alternative ideas.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "At the same time, we believe that the victory over ____ and hatred is achieved one person at a time.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is extremely important to ____ the installation with all parties involved.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A common kind of language problem is to fill in the ____ in a sentence with a missing word.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The sorting of students into homogeneous ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal ____ education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A great ____ of discussion focused on observations which could solve the mystery by testing the predictions of the various hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Everyone knows the dangers of smoking, yet hundred of young people start the ____ each year..", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We should avoid the error of assuming that we will ever be able to ____ the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Assign students to groups; establish rules for participation, and ____ jobs within each group.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In all cases, employers must offer ____ dates for a second-round interview if the date originally suggested is inconvenient.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is the duty of educators to ____ themselves carefully for each and every lesson.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As a business person who frequently deals with recent college graduates, I'd say that there has been a ____ deterioration of writing (and speaking) skills.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on ____ of another, the former steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We must hope that her heavy involvement in the school's sporting programme will not be to the ____ of her studies.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The student was reported to the headmaster for continually trying to ____ the class.", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was a very ____ problem. All the students were able to solve it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school has a ratio of ____ one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ service in Germany is much better than that in England.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The most ____ advice that you can give your children is: Be yourself.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government needs to find a better ____ for restricting the enormous amounts of money earned by top directors.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ criterion for successful teaching is the ability to interest the students.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "average", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "ordinary, typical"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is a very trivial example for demonstration purposes. However, the effect is ____ for more complex cases.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ issue is, and always has been, one of parenting.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people say that there should be ____ schools for students who are not so interested in writing or learning from books.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government raised taxes, deciding to ____ the loud protests in the media.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Problem behaviors were found to be ____ to drinking practices.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Looking up all the key words in an important ____ should be considered a background check for all literary analysis.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I can't ____ this beetle; I'll have to ask the science teacher what it is.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students, staff and faculty have a right to privacy and neither reporters nor the public should be allowed to ____ classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The police have decided not to ____ the identity of the men arrested for planting the bombs.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government blamed its ____ in the elections on failure to communicate its policies clearly enough.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Government scientists have found some red areas on the ____ of Jupiter, but they do not know yet what these signify.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There's no need to give an ____ answer, Two or three short sentences will be enough.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the firm eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Campuses must ____ an annual security report detailing statistics regarding crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Drug abusers also show prefrontal cortex ____ities; it is possible that ____ behaviour may be linked to drug use.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The forecast was for travel ____ to increase by 1 percent to 2 percent compared to last year.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ what a woman should do with her body.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is important that the government's proposals do not ____ the development of small businesses.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Both of these programs can be amended as needed to ____ a particular area of vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These facilities and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at considerable ____ to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The computer lab is ____ to the library.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "With her ____ it is not surprising that she has had problems in her new school.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to ____ herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to command serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will therefore attempt to ____ contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He was ____ yesterday for the third time this month. I presume he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They ____ their nutrients from the air and not from the plant on which they are growing.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Clinton certainly did not ____ these word games, but in recent years they have risen to a high art form in Washington.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ its tax proposals. They are less than clear to most people.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "On the rare ____ when Crockett looks upon Indians with anything less than pure hatred, his observations continue to feed upon common stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She has a lot of ____ in tennis; in fact she's the best player in her grade!", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Women often ____ less money that men doing the same job. This anomaly must be stopped.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Indeed, we know that the Fleming, who was first to invent the telescope, was a simple maker of ____ spectacles.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Telephone and telegraph ____ from the Greek words meaning far speak and far write.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows prior to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The management wanted to dismiss the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to ____ him.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The US government plan to develop weapons that can be used from space. Many scientists, however, ____ the proposals as unworkable.", "Opt_1": "govern", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this ____ of study will have abundant opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Cor-----nd: The dashes ____ to the number of letters missing from the word.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His ____ is that if we don't cut taxes, then unemployment will rise.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Science should be about objective facts, not ____ opinions.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Job applicants often find that their personal attributes match what a company values; when this occurs, you should ____ these attributes in your CV.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is the ____ of every teacher to be prepared for class and to do everything he or she can to help the students learn.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In ____ to make up a missed exam, you must produce written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a legitimate reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to ____ on future developments, we need to consider the actual and potential effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In our society, which is far from ____ in its beliefs and values, reaching consensus on any issue is significantly difficult.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ of the new hotel has been well-chosen: halfway between the airport and the beach.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you wish to remain at this school, you will have to ____ to its rules.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Scientists are working very hard to find a ____ for oil. They hope that one day cars will not pollute the atmosphere.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most simply, the strength of a ____ is measured by determining how much energy is required to break the ____.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Next year the school will ____ a policy of no smoking on campus for both teachers and students.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally rigid bodies ____ multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Your response was unclear. Could you please ____ it.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Medical scientists have done extensive research on individual drugs but they do not know so much how drugs ____ with each other.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The human mind cannot ____ the true nature of God, nor can the angels.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many parents ____ their children to the bedroom when they behave badly.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Here you can ____ areas for investment of resources to advance the University in its health sciences, education, research, service and outreach missions.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has made ____ arrangements to control the number of demonstrators on the streets.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company director decided to ____ his son as the new head of marketing.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In many cases what was once an ____ is now taken for granted. Remarkable inventions, once assimilated into daily life, become routine.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The doctor had to ____ the x-rays carefully to find any signs of abnormality.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It must be obvious what the primary theme of each ____ is, and how that theme connects with the paper's overall theme.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Financial aid is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families ____ the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "China did not ____ nuclear weapons. Having produced several hundred warheads, China stopped building up its military potential.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He is ____ considered a pioneer in this field, both in conducting research and in educating students to assume key positions in industry.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Everyone has the right to a ____ of living adequate for the health and well-being of himself and of his family, including food, clothing, and shelter.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is an ____ for a politician to be able to give a clear but concise statement of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While I don't present this as absolutely the ultimate ____ that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This survey examines attitudes ____ the campus-area housing market.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company's business partners are to a large ____ from Asia.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is feared that disagreement about what to do in Iraq will ____ the relationship between the USA and the UK.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail ____ to convince the reviewer that the problem is worth investigation.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government's election defeat is a ____ case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more time to your studies and a little less time to your sports.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Perhaps it is unfortunate that humor, by its nature of being based in ridicule, will always ____ someone.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many spiders can ____ seven different kinds of silk.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We must ____ the scientists and experts to make the right decisions to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school is located in the wooded ____ to the north west of Frankfurt.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this section of the survey, having an ____ privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a growing ____ to use the cell phone as the primary phone, without any need for landlines.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not ____ to Cheney's task force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Educational research is a useful tool for both ____ and theoretical problem solving.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As time went on scientists realized that mixing science and religion was ____ unnecessary and unproductive.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government needs to provide a better ____ for people to save more of their money.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In fact, Lenin knew that it was impossible to ____ a Communist International without the Germans.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The report shows how the mass media ____ affect adolescent smoking rates.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A half century ago the ____ over state regulation of railroads was the chief issue in Alabama politics.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Yet Bush also has adopted other, more ____ policy positions on guns and gun control.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Science should be about objective facts, not ____ opinions.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be ____ of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The latest ____ of his bad behaviour was to lock another student in the toilet.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to help each other, but is spite also part of the human condition?", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was agriculture that allowed civilizations to ____ growth.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These budgets must be very carefully designed as it is extremely difficult, if not impossible, to ____ the amount of the award once it has been granted.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students will ____ comprehensive analysis of several works and will compile a database of quality literature.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is very little ____ of the poor and middle class as our corrupt judges have developed a system called lawyer denial.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Working with the Teacher Assistant is not ____ but recommended.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If we are to ____ actions designed to reverse the pattern of current difficulties in Viet Nam we ought to lay the groundwork.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is a particular ____ to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who embody all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The name of this website is 'A ____ to learning English.'", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Through appointments and legislation the President was able to drain the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no ____ reaction.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Poor diet itself is not a cause of scoliosis, but maintaining a healthy diet can ____ the symptoms of scoliosis.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "From the airplane it was possible to see the ____ of the destruction caused in the earthquake.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you are an ____ with a permanent disability, you may be eligible to obtain a discount.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teacher should vary presentation styles and take into ____ diverse abilities and interests.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The idea was to ____ the possibility of a local court or government treating a foreign investor unfairly.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The new policy ____ that faculty members can no longer enter or modify grades for these classes online.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Oddly, however, the book is almost completely ____ in fictional representations of invalids.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "common"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While the Spartans were principally responsible for the victory, the Athenian fleet was probably the most important ____ of that victory.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her ability and experience to this new problem.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We often hear that now is the ____ of the most rapid change. From one perspective, this might be correct.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "No other ____ has been used more often or by more college teachers than the Minute Paper.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's difficult to ____ your good mood if it's hot and loud in the classroom, you have a headache, and the work is very boring.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of ____ guidance, but instead thought we should have the opportunity to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Despite the enormous amount of effort invested in her language teaching she was not able to ____ grammatical sentences.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Thanks to the accurate ____ of the witnesses, the police were able to identify the bank robbers.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ what a woman should do with her body.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government intends to ____ the information for itself. The public will not have access to it until the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and hence it should constitute the ____ of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people say that there should be ____ schools for students who are not so interested in writing or learning from books.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The explanation for this ____ decision lies in the immediate circumstances surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "From the airplane it was possible to see the ____ of the destruction caused in the earthquake.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I am no expert in animal behavior, but anyone with even a ____ knowledge of the field must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that credit cards are a temporary solution that can snowball into a ____ problem.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The current ____ of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students, staff and faculty have a right to privacy and neither reporters nor the ____ should be allowed to disrupt classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Stated simply, this principle means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks ____ like any other part.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not ____ more accurate results.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The first ____ of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to analyze and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "At the same time, we believe that the victory over ____ and hatred is achieved one person at a time.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Typical conversations involve a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans ____ as they grow.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Ambition was not an ____ of the female characters in his earlier films.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This ____ in your writing doesn't make sense. What are you trying to say?", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his intention to ____ at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you want to start a business you need a ____ amount of money.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "While I am not in favor of teaching creationism in public schools, I am also not ____ to having it presented and examined.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company made a radical reduction in its workforce in order to ____ its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has recently published reports about farming in the UK and illegal drug-taking. The ____ has created far more interest in the media.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The requirements ____ to decrease family and individual student control over the transition process.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your group will need to investigate the ____ characteristics of your city (such as mountains and lakes).", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government does not plan to ____ any more immigrants unless they can prove that their life is in danger in their own country.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All students whose college/university will be forwarding tuition payments will need to contact the OSA to find out the ____ procedure.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you accept a housing ____ in the Summer Allocation and subsequently cancel it or fail to move in, you are charged an administrative fee.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ information provides details on the spiking neuron model used in this work.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Specifically, you ____ that you were not provided with academic adjustments and auxiliary aids, and were not provided access to other services and programs at the College.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the urban districts, particularly in the Northern states, were totally averse to this development.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not ____ widely enough to provoke a revolution.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is not a business. Its goal is not to make a large profit, but to earn enough money to ____ the best possible education.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no ____ having a law if the police are not willing to enforce it.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A snowstorm failed to ____ soccer practice on the Inlet early last week.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If a child consistently begs to stay home from school, has extreme fear of being away from a parent etc., there may be a cause for ____ about the child.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government official wrote to ____ that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I'm not sure that his parents realize the ____ of the problems he is having in school.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She rejects, thereby, traditional feminine ideals of marriage and ____ behavior.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government was ____ successful in reducing teenage drinking during its first period in power.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The text should contain a ____ description of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not necessarily subjected to a ____ analysis, thus it will need to be evaluated by the user.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The online instructor must ____ the best practices of traditional teaching without the benefit of face-to-face interaction.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The documentation must consist of a comprehensive, typed report that states a specific, ____ diagnosis.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Unless we reverse the trend, the ____ will be a sustained contraction in the number and quality of staff scientists and research faculty.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to compile a full application including: ____ sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will ____ students of their ability to think for themselves if you never set them challenging questions.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The significant differences between the traditional and non-traditional student has prompted the question whether institutions need to ____ their teaching methods to fit the needs of the non-traditional student.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government was ____ successful in reducing teenage drinking during its first period in power.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students with Advanced Placement scores of 4 or 5 in English Language receive a ____ toward graduation but not toward the English major.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ sector of the UK economy is much more successful than the manufacturing sector.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's too easy to ____ all of the country's problems on the government.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you work hard all lesson, I will ____ you by letting you go to lunch five minutes early.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government neither intends to ____ on the event nor even to admit that it actually happened.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "That's probably the most fatuous ____ I've read on this website.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teacher did not completely ____ the students' suggestion, but she first needed to discuss it with the principal.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Under the new plan, the garden would remain at its current ____ on Walnut and Virginia streets and the pumping station would be built on the northeast.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of constant guidance, but ____ thought we should have the opportunity to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Everyone knows the dangers of smoking, yet hundred of young people start the ____ each year..", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Under the new plan, the garden would remain at its current ____ on Walnut and Virginia streets and the pumping station would be built on the northeast.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school ____ it impossible to fulfill its promise to reduce tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her parents failed to ____ the bad influence of her new friends until it was too late.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Newton's Laws provide a good ____ of the flight of a baseball.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please ____ that I have your report by next Friday.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "New challenges, opportunities, and demands are necessary to ensure that creativity and motivation do not ____ away.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "diverge", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This makes Kraay's work an unreliable ____ to whether globalisation really is making people in those countries better off.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To include an image on your website, you will need to ____ the image into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The last week of the tennis tournament will ____ the first week of the Olympic Games.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We have never in history needed to ____ of so much waste as we do today.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The unit did not ____ nuclear weapons in as much detail as some of my students would have liked.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the gap between North and South campuses with two concerts that ____ symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The workers did not ____ to lose their jobs. It was the managers who made the mistakes, not them.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have ____ problems than children in more stable placements.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Recent research shows bias ____ African American mothers of any class who don't work.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My biggest regret about the book is that Gruchy did not ____ his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is no need to ____ in detail the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a sharp ____ between Japan's fairly rigid hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time prior to the ____ date.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government is finding it difficult to break the cycle of poverty and ____ school performance.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I'm sorry, but I will ____ not be able to come to the meeting next week.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Program is designed to ____ researchers whose ISBM-supported work appears in the academic literature.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many British citizens and their political and ____ leaders were suspicious of Napoleon's motives and would not cooperate, so the tunnel project was abandoned.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Her consistent efforts throughout the school year are certain to ____ excellent results in her final examinations.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors are advising older patients to have an injection as a precaution ____ influenza this winter.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is NOT a ____ statistic and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV ____ the government will declare its intention to reduce taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance rank is ____ of maternal rank, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest rank between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unlike other animals, humans have no ____ for survival; we often choose to do things that may be detrimental to our health.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The final ____ of rebuilding the school will be finished by the end of the vacation.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was no limit, it seemed, to what the terrorists who ____ America were prepared to do.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "DeRosa's success is a ____ example of how the right environment and excellent faculty really can cause a scholarly transformation.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Bush's principal ____ for re-election is his war on terrorism, but in fact that's one of the principal reasons he should not be re-elected.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Teachers should not ____ the discussion or act as the last word on a student's artwork.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government's ____ in his second term of office is to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Lincoln, while receiving a majority vote ____ northerners, did not receive a majority of ALL the popular votes.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The current program review process is not very ____ because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We should agree on our general plan first. We can talk later about the important ____ of who will pay.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Downloading and reading this letter does not ____ acceptance to the First-Year course.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most powerful typhoon in over a ____ should break south of Shanghai early on Wednesday.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The debate over whether North Korea will ____ and whether the United States should promote its ____ has paralyzed American policymaking.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government wants to ____ young mothers in poor areas to attend parenting classes.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Listening to the people is an ____ aspect of good government.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If someone invites you to their party, it's polite to send them a ____ and tell them if you can come or not.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your final writing must ____ to your research notes, otherwise you risk being accused of plagiarism.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Could you please ____ the homework for me? I'm not sure I understand.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school has installed emergency buttons in each classroom as a ____ against intruders.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "California's medical schools and major teaching hospitals are directly and ____ responsible for more than 200000 full-time jobs.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The controversy resulted from the fact that the Jews agreed to the resolution but the ____ Arabs refused to acknowledge the Israeli State.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The world's largest film ____ is in Hollywood, Los Angeles.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After these two periods of individual work time that did not ____ any teacher instruction, the students presented their work to the class.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was also no apparent ____ of an attempt to measure the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It would not be wise to ____ from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Her work has continued to ____ since the divorce of her parents.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When dealing with a real, physical system such as a robot, however, this ____ is simply not practical.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is too early to ____ whether the government's plan to reduce child poverty have been successful or not.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ a better impulse for people to save more of their money.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "But when planned and ____ policy forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "former", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can ____ make cannabis legal and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A book published in the regular way must ____ mainly upon its own merits for its success.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She chose to ____ the hypothesis that there is an increased risk of having a second child with the same disorder.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is essential to consider her difficulties at school in the ____ of her chaotic home life.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most of Africa suffers to some ____ from similar issues: weak institutions, stagnant economies, ethnic conflict, etc.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was a very ____ test. Everyone got 100%.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The university intend to make some changes in its admissions policy, but it cannot yet ____ what those changes will be.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Production of oil and gas will ____ unless new reserves of oil and gas are discovered and developed.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school cannot ____ its teachers to give up smoking, but it can tell them not to smoke inside the building.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This certificate program is a series of fully online courses that will show you how to ____ and deliver a quality course via the Internet.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although the agreement was compulsory rather than voluntary, it led to ____ military reforms along French lines.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The cost of gas (petrol) will continue to ____ as the price of oil goes up or down.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Participants donate a small amount of blood or saliva, which will be used as a ____ to blood from children with genetic diseases.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is really no ____ in arguing which approach is better.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It offers an effective solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills ____ as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Injuries occur when there is a certain blow or ____ against the head, damaging the interior of the brain.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To ____ these opportunities, information systems will need to sense and act as well as compute.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This makes Kraay's work an unreliable ____ to whether globalisation really is making people in those countries better off.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to ____ to avoid an ambiguous answer.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I believe that people often ____ the hardships the parents experience if their child has a learning disability.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Perhaps the most elaborate example of an arthropod joint, ____ one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Much of the literature reviewed by the committee failed to specify in sufficient detail the definition of a medication ____ used in the study.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Medical scientists have shown it to be a ____ that lying in bed is the best way to heal a bad back.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction ____ junior faculty, it must make an effort to align its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ quickly throughout the classroom to make sure that everyone understands the task, then return to help students who are having difficulty.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ is the most common teaching style at university. There is not so much question and answer as in schools.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I'm trying to ____ a machine that will do my homework for me. - Good luck!", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to ____ people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The demonstrators failed to ____ the progress of the Olympic torch through the city streets.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To accurately determine mass balance, stakes were placed in the ____ clean ice areas of the glacier.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you are going on the field trip, do not forget to ____ if you need a special diet.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Among college students, concerns about body ____ and weight obsession remain widespread.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If we ____ just a little more, we will see that random is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The study did not discover any significant ____ between the type of music and the amount of stress.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His written work is actually very good, but he has ____ problems with the difficult English spelling system.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school has installed emergency buttons in each classroom as a ____ against intruders.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an attack on Chinese industry, but a dispute over a ____ issue.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A popular kind of literature these days is about the lives of ordinary people who are caught up in ____ events such as war or terrorism.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an odd number will always ____ an even number.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In our previous class on binary counting, we found a way to ____ numbers using just two digits, 0 and 1.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Since Ramadan emphasizes community aspects and since everyone eats dinner at the same time, Muslims often invite one another to ____ in the Ramadan evening.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Each programme is designed to give students the opportunity to explore significant social, ____ and environmental issues using an innovative comparative model.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Design your syllabus so that it communicates to students what you expect them to learn and also how to ____ in achieving the learning goals for your course.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Every new car that is produced must ____ to standards that minimize pollution.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Remember that more than one factor may be the ____ of a problem and that symptoms may often overlap in their appearance.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "How can you tell if the book, article, website, or other ____ you located is a valid, credible source?", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I don't have very much knowledge in the ____ of electronics.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is the wrong ____ to have when considering the true dangers the culture of alcohol presents to the campus.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to ____ to changes in society and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to ____ to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ancient Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government is thinking of passing a law that will require all house owners to ____ their oil heating system for one that runs on gas.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you do not ____ to the rules of the school, you will be asked to leave.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A concise and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too ____ or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Given the abundance of oxygen and silicon in the crust, it should not be surprising that the most ____ minerals in the earth's crust are the silicates.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The thesis is unoriginal and lacks ____ into the key issues.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Each section of the book, is represented by a family, which was chosen as an ____ family representing that country.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The prime ____ of a strong academic vocabulary is that it helps you to read school textbooks more efficiently.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My father's company is going to facilitate our move to Germany by employing an ____ to help us find a house here.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The UK Highway ____ is the book of road rules that must be learned by new drivers.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "All new systems to the data center will need to undergo a security scan or audit ____ to installation.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is apparent that you made no ____ to learn the words for the test.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Those who could not transform, chose not to, or who were considered a threat to the ____ were imprisoned and eliminated.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is unclear whether this facility will be able to ____ complete missiles or only some major component.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A company's success or continuation should not ____ on the service of outside in____ent contractors.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The management is considering removing the salesmen's ____ to use company cars at the weekend for private purposes.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "However, because The Dream intends to interest both lay and professional readers, it is unfortunate that she failed to ____ a glossary of significant terms.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government needs to find a better ____ for restricting the enormous amounts of money earned by top directors.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government made the ____ decision to kill all cows in the area before the disease could spread.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Science should be about objective facts, not ____ opinions.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You may need to ____ to the terms and scope of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "reduce", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This international ____ course has been especially created for international students in their final stage of studies in Law.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it reliable and ____ decided to ignore it.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "London is becoming more and more unpleasant. The government needs to drastically increase the ____ for dropping litter.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, thus is unable to ____ insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The data is ambiguous as some analysts ____ this figure according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She recognized the importance of introducing a plan that was ____ enough to meet the changing demands of the university.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "China is able to manufacture goods cheaply because ____ costs are low.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "But when planned and ____ policy forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A hunt for hazardous asteroids by University of Hawaii astronomers who use a ____ search strategy has paid off.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Library and information science students must be taught how to exploit the resources that will allow them to anticipate the future and ____ becoming irrelevant as information professionals.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company's ____ for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this figure by 40%.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his intention to ____ at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Emma was ____ of these various and strongly held opinions, through professional periodicals.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Requiring students to leave the school building at lunchtime is not a very popular ____ from the new principal.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some solutions exist to improve the performance of these devices, but ____ there are limitations how accessible they can be made.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This review found that some guidelines and standards for reprocessing rigid laryngoscopes are incomplete, inadequate, and not ____ with one another.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Once Windows Movie Maker has opened, you will need to ____ the video clip that you would like to edit.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Two thousand years from now, an archaeologist will find little ____ of the millions of web pages that have been updated in the last hour.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We still don't know if this is really the correct mechanism to ____ the imbalance between matter and antimatter that we observe.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The CLAS Institute identifies, evaluates, and promotes ____ and appropriate early intervention and preschool practices that are sensitive to diverse cultural and linguistic backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "On the ship, every ____ room and corner was turned into dormitory space; cots were set up to accommodate the overflow.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "At weddings the speeches usually ____ the food.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "His current measurement results are not precise enough to identify exactly the ____ that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early ____ start-ups in the environment of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The University may ____ the Contract at any time by giving thirty (30) days written notice to the Contract.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Those who will be attending the event should try to make it to the Speedway early to ____ the rush hour traffic.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Of course she makes grammar mistakes; she is at the ____ stage of learning English.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We also want to speak openly about the question of whether the German radio should ____ so-called jazz music.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Ambition was not an ____ of the female characters in his earlier films.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Plagiarism is easy to ____ but often hard to define. This is partly because the legal rules differ sharply from the ethical ones.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The explanation for this extraordinary decision lies in the ____ circumstances surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government decided to increase its ____ to the countries of eastern Africa.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If we want this plan to be a success, we need to ____ our resources very carefully.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some information is collected on our behalf by outside agencies in ____ to provide services to our visitors.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We held that the entry was illegal because police failed to ____ their purpose before using the crowbar to pry the door open.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is the single most important deed a district judge can perform in the ____ of his duties.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you want to be successful in business, it is certainly an ____ to be able to speak more than one language.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company has decided to ____ its main attention to increasing business in the developing Chinese market.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The students ____ that I promised to show a DVD on in class today, but I cannot remember doing so.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to ____ its responsibility to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We all have to ____ differences of opinion in the political world and, in order to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government needs to provide a better ____ for people to save more of their money.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Scientists are working very hard to find a ____ for oil. They hope that one day cars will not pollute the atmosphere.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Plants that possess certain traits or characteristics not common to the ____ species are referred to as biotypes.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A verbal ____ is impossible to prove, and the organization will always maintain that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This course traces the ancient ____ of the hero by reading selected works by authors such as Homer, Plutarch and Caesar.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He is an American ____ which obviously puts him in a different category from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ between Russia's dominant military power and our own inferior power could not be bridged overnight.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My ____ tells me that there is more to her learning problems than the parents are willing to say.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The June 1992 Gender Equity Study found a significant ____ in salaries between men and women.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school is will continue to ____ problems in its attempt to attract new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This semester-long project begins with an overview in which students think about how to ask scientific questions and ____ hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "On the rare occasion when Crockett looks upon Indians with anything less than ____ hatred, his observations continue to feed upon common stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A ____ and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too vague or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The only disappointing part of the book is a ____ of the third chapter, which is devoted to an interesting but much too brief discussion of FDR's foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This we know: the earth does not ____ to man, man ____s to the earth.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The prime minister is today expected to ____ the date of the next election.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Turkish law requires foreign scholars to ____ formal permission to carry out research at institutions in Turkey.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You should be able to ____ the answer if you think carefully enough.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We were not able to demonstrate statistically significant differences in ____ or quality.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school gave a ____ warning to the teacher who had arrived late to school several times that month.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The word give is substituted for the word ____ to express more clearly the intent of the section.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from power cycle failure, but this is not a ____ for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "concern", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The \"Maximize\" position says that we should give ____ to whatever treatment produces the greatest net health benefit.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's not easy to ____ yourself when you're not going out and actually preparing for an opponent.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The spaceship has been sending back ____ images of Jupiter as it flies past on its way to the edge of the solar system.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of new doctors is getting low. Some remote parts of the country will be without medical services if this situation does not change.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The airport authorities have decided to ____ passengers to carry only very small amounts of liquid onto the plane.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "prohibit", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to ban, disallow"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Why, Graeme Newman asks, has ____ after ____ failed to halt the spread of crime?", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse community of education and research institutions vested in the ____ goal of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Perhaps the very hot, dry weather we have had for the last 6 weeks will convince some doubters that ____ warming is really happening.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is easy to use the internet to ____ a lot of information. Whether it is of good quality is a different matter!", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design phase will ____ that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "include", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Mobile phones enable parents to keep in ____ with their children when they are out with their friends.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The student said that his dog had eaten his homework. The teacher did not believe him but could not ____ what he said.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Every necessary ____ has been taken to provide up-to-date, accurate information in this website.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Strauss said his health started to ____ and he was placed on the transplant recipient waiting list.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of course work, but it must ____ achievement that is over and above regular course activities.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although his letter did not stipulate Atlanta as the ____ of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Under these treaties, US warships did not have to ____ the nature of the weapons they carried.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The head teacher decided to push through her idea though most of the teachers were ____ it.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We should not ____ the costs, minimize the benefits of what we have already achieved, or downplay the risk of failure to persevere.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We need to address the issue of absenteeism and lower productivity ____ working parents who worry that their kids are not safe.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been ____ before, and it is apparent that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an ____ occasion to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many people buy ____ vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their regular food.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You may have learned the steps of the scientific method but, in your preparation, failed to ____ each step with an example.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some solutions ____ to improve the performance of these devices, but naturally there are limitations how accessible they can be made.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The course is intended to ____ a lot of class discussion.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an urgent meeting in order to ____ what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The journey to peace and prosperity in the ____ can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many people believe that the 'war on terror' will be a ____ war.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "On the back of this form or on a separate sheet, write a thorough ____ describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you currently do not possess the ____ to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for the bad test scores is that the teacher was new and inexperienced.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to enable him to make a ____ decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "One danger of any powerful ____ is that, at the height of its power, people confuse the ____ and the thing that is being compared to it.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and worth of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They still ____ copying the work from the internet, but I ran a Google search and found it immediately.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Research into heart disease has revealed a clear pattern: those who smoke too much, drink too much and do not exercise enough are the most likely to ____ from it.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is noted that the university regulations ____ that a course can be offered only if a minimum number of students is enrolled.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Germany had to accept a ____ peace treaty after being defeated in the first world war.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not ____ it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in order to extend a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to ____ your instinct as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The drugs are used to enhance ____ artificially to the degree that they give athletes a competitive edge.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Because of the interactive nature of the classroom, absences will significantly ____ your performance in the course.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to ____ the throne of Armenia, could not conceal his discontent.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company has decided to ____ its main attention to increasing business in the developing Chinese market.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I have no ____ to students wearing hats in the classroom, but many teachers do.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will generate much debate in the classroom, mainly ____ graduate students.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A ____ and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too vague or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The United States is a nation pulling ____ to a degree unknown in the last 25 years.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school will ____ use of the library for all students unless the student who damaged the photocopier is found.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV broadcast the government will declare its intention to ____ taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A student seeking a ____ in this field of study will have abundant opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A book published in the regular way must depend mainly upon its ____ merits for its success.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many talented local young people have had to ____ graduate or professional education because of lack of access to such programs.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to ____ profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are ____ parts of the planet that have not yet been explored. These are all on the ocean floor.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Carrying a large ____ of money is not a crime.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A doctor will usually ask her patient many questions in order to make a ____ of the illness.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The sorting of students into ____ ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The first effort to ____ a revised policy started during the mid-1980s and failed to culminate in a new agreement.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the ____ of learning received by distance education students and regular students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you want to know whether an phrase is ____ or not, look it up in Google.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of constant guidance, but ____ thought we should have the opportunity to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to focus not only on the skills and knowledge related to the high stakes tests but also the skills and knowledge to perform more ____ tasks.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not ____ to 100% because many students were neutral on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to dictate the ____ of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Can you please use a ____ ruler to draw straight lines, not the side of your book.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to differentiate poor work that is ____ to laziness and poor work that is ____ to inability.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The global ____ agreements have failed to include meaningful, enforceable labour or environmental standards.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further instance of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to ____ requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to dictate the ____ of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people ____ before eating raw fish for the first time. They are not sure what it will taste like.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Omitting the transportation costs would ____ the company's financial position.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Very pure water does not ____ electricity well compared with contaminated water because it contains no inorganic ions.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The two scholars are impressed with the ____ audience of readers their blog drew after their first three postings on Dec. 5, 2004.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are ____ students from Korea at Frankfurt International School.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will ____ no credit for work that has simply been copied from the internet.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has set the ambitious ____ of halving child poverty by the year 2020.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you choose not to ____ or to withdraw from the study at any time, there will be no penalty.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a regular basis to incorporate new understanding.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Beyond this, if you have a ____ reason for absence or coming in late, such as a documented medical excuse, you should provide that information to the instructor.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The computer manager is trying to ____ who has been sending email spam to all the teachers and students.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To accommodate the great power ____ now rapidly occurring in Asia, the United States needs vigorous preparation by its executive branch and Congress.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "help"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Older people should have a ____ check-up at the doctors at least once a year.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Visit our web page Phases of the Moon for a more detailed explanation and a clear ____ that shows the phases of our moon.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Important politicians are usually surrounded by bodyguards whose job is to ____ them.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Modern computers can ____ the equivalent of many millions of pages of writing.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not ____ that he could have gained such a good grade without help from someone else.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "credible", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "believable"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Mathematics course: Students will read aloud verbal problems in class and state the meaning in their ____ words.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ability to communicate accurately and effectively is a ____ component of the curriculum.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Powerpoint presentations do not always impress, ____ if the actual content is poor.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school does not own the sports hall. It belongs to the ____ council, which charges the school to use it.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of equipment like a camera, it helps to have a ____ to look at.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government should not ____ its tax policies on what newspaper editors tell it to do.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Princeton University computer scientist Edward Felton has decided not to publish a paper on how his research team broke the ____ of copyright protection.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You should ____ your name from the copies of the items you submit.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It's a serious attack on any community's authority to develop and ____ housing policies without consultation.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "But, for their part, the Syrian leaders failed to ____ for Israel to have rights to some of that water.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the key words used and the ____ claims made in ads, the more aware you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you want to ____ in school you will have to study hard!", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is, once again, not an argument ____ bilingual education, because studies have shown that children in well- designed bilingual programs do well.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is ____ a reason why the majority of past safety research has focused on organization and actions.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Politics is still a ____ male profession.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He wants to get a job in the engineering ____ when he leaves school.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Religion is an ____ in which many people have very strong feelings.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The report shows how the mass media ____ affect adolescent smoking rates.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The author had failed to annotate his report, so it was impossible to check the ____ of his claims.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "So, what's the point of all this hindsight and what do we stand to ____ from it?", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "On the whole the great ____ of Canadian immigration of the past generation has been drawn from the English-speaking countries.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we reflect just a little more, we will see that random is ____ the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ information provides details on the spiking neuron model used in this work.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In Ancient Rome not every ____ had equal rights.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is a ____ to think that you can put off working until the week before the exam and still pass it.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The teacher was asked to ____ after it was discovered that he had lied about his absence from school.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is the ____ of educators to prepare themselves carefully for each and every lesson.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many people think that there is ____ any chance of peace in the Middle East. The situation in that part of the world is just too complex.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Television and the other news media have helped to ____ the person and the institution of the presidency.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Abnormal results do not diagnose birth defects, they just ____ that follow-up tests are necessary for further clarification.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The committee will ____ the process by which the decision was made.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She lied to the ____ and cheated in her test, but because of her family situation, it was decided to allow her to stay.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will ____ more rapidly if you make more effort.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the disaster did not ____ until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "transform", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often completely)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Parents and children often ____ in their opinions on the importance of keeping bedrooms clean and tidy.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government intends to ____ a new organization to help young people find suitable jobs.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Not any of these persons shall perform or ____ any practice that may damage the reputation of the university.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A ____ in the USA at the moment is whether to allow illegal immigrants to stay or not.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more secure ____ unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, owe a huge ____ to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more on the books that you read. It's not enough to just write what happens.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is ____ unusual considering the 1997 survey's response of 41%.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ goal of teaching is to teach students how to teach themselves.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to ____ the plan on a regular basis to incorporate new understanding.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To ____ for the credit, fuel cells are required to be 500 watt capacity or greater with a generation efficiency of 30% or greater.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you want to run this software, you will need to ____ the operating system.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Every second ____ of Frankfurt is a non-native speaker of German.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Director develops and oversees an ____ program of professional development and leadership training for history and social science teachers.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "From my perspective as a teacher and parent, I would say that her difficulties in school are ____ to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There was little ____ to the government's proposals to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The accident was clearly not the ____ of the employee or his supervisor.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Everyone should ____ together to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Occasional personal use of university computing resources for other purposes is permitted when it does not ____ a significant amount of those resources.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "consume", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to use, or use up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you cannot obtain such a statement, you must ____ that you have contacted your employer and that the employer was unable to assist you with the refund.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Tilghman has appointed a group of faculty members to ____ her on how the University can best respond to the challenges and opportunities in the international arena.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Due to the severe shortage of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to ____ a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "On the ship, every ____ room and corner was turned into dormitory space; cots were set up to accommodate the overflow.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teachers fear that the problems in the Middle East may strain the ____ between some of the Arab and Israeli students at the school.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to ____ its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is a very trivial example for demonstration purposes. However, the ____ is similar for more complex cases.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Next you need to formulate a search ____ so you can conduct a database search.", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It should be ____ that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the prime cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Asia is our closest region and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and ____ culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "exchange", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ to be recognized, to be considered important is not superficial. It is a basic human drive.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some people have radical ideas about education. For example, that children should be allowed to choose whether or not to ____ lessons.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If the human body is weak or cold, it is less able to ____ infection.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government's proposals will have a ____ effect on the education of every child in the country.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When they did investigations after 9-11, one of the major things that they came up with was that the various government agencies did not ____ the dots.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school wanted to ____ students from families outside the usual sphere of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This project involves students in the process of learning in an attempt to ____ their skills and their successes across all areas of the course.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was difficult for the two sides in the dispute to find a ____ time to meet.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many large companies employ people to analyze a ____ such as the way people spend their money on holiday, etc.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When he left home he planned to ____ from Christianity to Buddhism, but then he decided he didn't believe in any god.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The topic of child deaths in the nineteenth century is one which could ____ fail to interest any serious scholar of the period.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Stopping work to look after a new-born child must not be allowed to ____ with a woman's career chances.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It only drew more attention to the 13-year-old Robertson panel report and the CIA's ____ in the investigation of UFOs.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "role", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "job or function", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Parents have ____ over their children until the children leave home.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As people are defining a process or a problem, sometimes solutions ____ in that moment, in the detail of their description.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A ____ error in editing is to fix a word or phrase at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Her work has continued to ____ since the divorce of her parents.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "List the specific things you did to achieve strong ____ in your project.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most famous footballers and film stars need an ____ to take care of their contracts.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government expects to ____ resistance from some people to the prohibition of smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ an incentive for long-term unemployed people to start looking for work again.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has set a clear ____ on how much pollution factories are allowed to release into the atmosphere every year.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With his difficult family ____ it is not really surprising that he's having trouble in school.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has increased ____ spending by 50% in the last two years.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Problems in school often ____ problems at home.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Campuses must ____ an annual security report detailing statistics regarding crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Government scientists have found some red areas on the ____ of Jupiter, but they do not know yet what these signify.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This page contains a ____ outline to be used as a guide for the creation of a strong outline.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Choose active, ____ verbs to invigorate your scientific or engineering professional papers, thesis, and reports.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ was not visible in its entirety on the computer screen.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Researchers at the university plan to ____ a survey into what makes people over-drink.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These results are interesting, though not ____ to interpret.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "credible", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "believable"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of the student as the school's primary customer provides an important guiding principle for many of today's school reforms.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The atmosphere between the workers and the management improved when ____ working time was introduced.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ vocabulary as the single most important aspect of learning English.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an urgent meeting in order to ____ what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam depend very heavily on ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As each hydrogen only has one electron to ____ in the formation of chemical bonds, it is impossible to connect more than two hydrogen atoms to each other.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government generally did not take steps to ____ or punish the most serious cases of abuse.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company was unable to ____ its recent good trade figures.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an ____ with a great volume of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please write a brief ____ of the causes of the first world war. Write no more than 300 words.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school has installed emergency buttons in each classroom as a ____ against intruders.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Increased ____ caused consumers to spend more and firms to invest more.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has invited the ____ community to its Open Day.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These findings suggest that something in the brain's pain-processing and pain-killing systems may ____ by race and ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government's plan is for at least 50% of school leavers to ____ a university or college.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some parents or guardians who place their children temporarily in foster care do so because they cannot ____ their abilities to raise their children.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There's no need to give an ____ answer, Two or three short sentences will be enough.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Despite the fact that there was a stream on the land, he could not ____ of the property at any price.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When a ____ of wood is gently put into still water, it will descend by the force of gravity, until it has displaced a quantity of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "That's the third time she's been late in the last week. I think I need to ____ the matter with her parents.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The University may ____ the Contract at any time by giving thirty (30) days written notice to the Contract.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Bulgaria is to face a severe ____ of teachers within the next three years, education experts declared.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To ____ the project, a special event will commence at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although the agreement was ____ rather than voluntary, it led to substantial military reforms along French lines.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not the only ____ of teaching we use at the university; instead we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Library and information science students must be taught how to exploit the resources that will allow them to ____ the future and avoid becoming irrelevant as information professionals.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great distance from her primary focus as an ____ for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and worth of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An enormous amount of research has been conducted into the ____ by which young children learn to speak.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Entrants in this competition are challenged to use or extend the building's ____ infrastructure in the service of the people who learn and teach here.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "About a quarter of the elementary and secondary students typically did not ____ with the teacher at all during class.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The manager has decided form a committee to ____ the recent increase in theft from the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Due to her student teaching commitments Murray was unable to ____ this year's event.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "World War II was a turning ____ because, for the first time, women were allowed to join the military.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Illegal drugs are grouped into one or other ____ according to how dangerous they are considered.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The assessment was not independent of influence by Coca-Cola (i.e. the final report appeared to have been edited by Coca-Cola ____ to its release.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He did not manage to develop a particularly good ____ in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ resulted from the fact that the Jews agreed to the resolution but the local Arabs refused to acknowledge the Israeli State.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a widespread belief that scaling up HIV ____ counseling and testing (VCT) programs in Africa will have large prevention benefits.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "often"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in society and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made ____ through translations of ancient Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When attempting to select a food ____ for an on-campus event, please be sure to ask the following questions.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a serious shortage of workers in the ____ of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ from Frankfurt to Oberursel is about 12 kilometers.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Despite the enormous amount of ____ invested in her language teaching she was not able to construct grammatical sentences.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many language teachers believe that their learners should use only ____ materials, not ones especially made for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students needed to devote considerable time to recognizing the three ____ tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In this next task you need to ____ with the person sitting next to you.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "cooperate", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Supreme Court held that the free exercise of religion did not ____ an Orthodox Jew to wear a yarmulke when he was on duty as an officer of law.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "With an ____ in the price of food and necessaries, the natural price of labor will rise; with the fall in their price, the natural price of labor will fall.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has little chance of success in its ____ to reduce crime unless it creates more jobs.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The time when Hitler was leader of Germany is possibly the most terrible ____ in all of history.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most companies ____ to replace machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Another well-known ____ of marijuana is its ability to increase appetite.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You should ____ your name from the copies of the items you submit.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In sports events it is a good idea at the start of the game to ____ energy that you are going to need later.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your ____ task for this lesson is to work together to prepare a presentation on air pollution.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ how much people should or should not drink.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Each College or School should ____ the teaching of basic technology skills at the earliest level possible.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of the aid money that has been allocated to Afghanistan has been wasted.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not enough to ____ children not to play with fireworks. It should be illegal for children to buy them.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If your condition is ____ and is impacting only attendance, make sure you follow up with your professors and contact the Dean of Students Office.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In some countries anyone caught taking drugs can expect a very ____ punishment.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ancient puzzle involving three pegs, and an ____ number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The producer of these webpages has long been an ____ of the value of computers in language teaching.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an attack on Chinese industry, but a ____ over a legitimate issue.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam depend very heavily on ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the key words used and the explicit claims made in ads, the more ____ you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As the advisor, you often have other responsibilities that do not always ____ giving undivided attention to the organization.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "exchange", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "That was not a very ____ thing to do.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is no need to ____ in detail the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is not an ____ supply of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "But, for their part, the Syrian leaders failed to ____ for Israel to have rights to some of that water.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The bank didn't think that her idea would ____ enough money so they refused to finance it.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This international degree course has been especially created for international students in their final ____ of studies in Law.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is a very clear ____ in the school for expelling students who do not follow the rules.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ problem is that we don't have enough money.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is not a business. Its goal is not to make a large profit, but to earn enough money to ____ the best possible education.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The goals are to answer some of the most ____ questions to advance significantly our scientific knowledge about Mars.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I asked for a ____ summary of what happened. So why have you given me a 20-page report?", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can ____ sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a fund to give someone the opportunity to pursue higher ____ at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This international degree course has been especially created for international students in their final ____ of studies in Law.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has given \ufffd\ufffd10 million to fight AidS in Africa, but some people believe that this ____ is not sufficient.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My ____ is to be your teacher, not to entertain you with endless youTube clips.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The parents decided to ____ against the school's expulsion their son.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The new manager needs time to ____ her own style of leadership.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "encourage", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some parents do not ____ how difficult it is to provide an education that will meet the needs of all students.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students worked in groups to prove (or disprove) a ____ of mathematical statements.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When a satisfactory ____ has been found using limits, the limits should then be removed if possible, in order to perform or re-perform the error.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Can you please give me the final ____ of your writing? This looks like your first draft before you corrected the spelling and grammar.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Institute must take greater measures to assure students that they need not ____ consequences when seeking medical help for substance abuse.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When you approach the city, you will ____ the many disused factories.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Political Bureau will work to ensure the smooth ____ of the reform of the administrative system.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Since the early 1990s, the number of smokers has continued to decrease but at the more gradual ____ of 5.2% annually.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but ____ language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most teachers are ____ to students wearing hats or chewing gum in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Kiewra found that students who did not even attend the ____ but reviewed the instructor notes performed better than students who did attend but failed to take notes.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Rules do not usually stimulate creativity or passion; rather they ____ conformity and make us fear change.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You should use the bathroom ____ to coming to class.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Traveling really gives students a better ____ of the world.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "surplus", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you ____ your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its structure or content.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is no magic ____ for getting better in English, but lots of reading is an easy and enjoyable way to improve.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Ours is the only ____ that can prevent a massive loss of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "From the end of the Great Depression to the mid-1970s economic growth was ____ and its benefits were widely spread throughout the society.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India acquire cars.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Unfortunately, heroines of this sort are not ____ in oral tales, and do not exist at all in any of the Grimm tales.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company was heavily in ____ after investing a lot of money in new machinery.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not ____ widely enough to provoke a revolution.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Dr. Glick is an ____ in community and public health nursing programs and issues.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These results are interesting, though not ____ to interpret.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The cost of oil has risen sharply this year, with the ____ that people are having to pay a lot more to heat their homes in the winter.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Even though you may know your housemates well, you should always take the ____ to lock the door. Windows should also be secured.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While we are less concerned with the politics of Nigeria, we understand that a ____ domestic situation would be to our advantage.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I think we should ____ her work more closely for the next few weeks. She needs to know that we are concerned about her progress.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Every 10 years the government carries out a ____ survey of all households in the country. This is called a census.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Lack of ____ revenue often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Since Ramadan emphasizes ____ aspects and since everyone eats dinner at the same time, Muslims often invite one another to share in the Ramadan evening.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I ____ the reasons for your failure to hand in the work on time. Nevertheless, our policy requires me to give you a zero.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the disaster did not ____ until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Good writing is concise. A sentence should ____ no unnecessary words, a paragraph no unnecessary sentences.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Each student must ____ in a group project during the second half of the semester.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an odd number will always ____ an even number.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The police ____ found it difficult to explain why the wrong man had been arrested.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your work will be penalized if you do not ____ it by the assigned deadline.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The police could find no ____ of the girl who was kidnapped from her hotel.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to adjust the ____ of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you come from an EU country and follow a study programme in the Netherlands, you may be eligible for a ____ for these tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a ____ of its books to display to teachers.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police could find no ____ of the girl who was kidnapped from her hotel.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to speculate on future developments, we need to consider the actual and ____ effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was only one stage in a long ____ that did not come to a legal end until 1971.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A link is provided in case the visitor wishes to return to the Search page to ____ other products in the same category.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is inevitable that any complex ____ will have some sort of taxation system.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids ____ sound better than air.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My goal this term is to ____ my mathematics and science grades.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These three young women have exhibited the kind of inner strength, commitment to friendship, patience and self-control that one ____ sees.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will lessen your chances of success if you are ____ from school so often.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is ____ a surprise that national governments have failed to solve global problems, since they have also failed to solve their own domestic problems.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For some people the ____ of a car is more important than its price or performance.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is no point having a law if the police are not willing to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This means that you will be able to add money from your bank ____ to your StanfordCardPlan using this new online service.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Your reading is improving fast, but you should not ____ your writing. It is through writing that you show your teachers what you know or have understood.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Can you please ____ this letter to your parents?", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Contact between infected and uninfected people can ____ disease.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of the Urselbach river is high in the Taunus hills behind the school.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "All of those guidelines put together would make it nearly impossible to ____ a piece of art or literature.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to procure a variety of ____ to complete this class.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school is located in the wooded ____ to the north west of Frankfurt.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Under the new programme, employees will ____ to accumulate the same amount of paid time off as they did in the old programme.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has so far refused to make ____ its plans for the continued presence of its soldiers in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors are ____ encouraged by the reduction in the numbers of young people starting to smoke.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school's decision to ____ the tuition fees will have a serious implication on the number of students who plan to attend.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The most important ____ of living near the school is that I can go home for lunch every day.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between the sports of mountain-climbing and table tennis. In the first you can get killed; in the second usually not.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new law will ____ unmarried mothers.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first ____ all possibilities for Federal and state financial aid programs before seeking alternative loans.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to ____ sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this figure by 40%.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This process is more ____ in those sciences in which the technological requirements have increased to a significant extent.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She is being ____ concerned about the exams. She will certainly pass.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Wildcats, however, were unable to ____ the scoring opportunities into points.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She did not fear death, but saw it as a welcome ____ or respite from earthly existence.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "release", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The doctor had to ____ the x-rays carefully to find any signs of abnormality.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The student must defend the thesis before a ____ of three or more faculty members.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government expects to ____ resistance from some people to the prohibition of smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "overcome", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to conquer, defeat"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This could substantially change the nature of the Internet we have come to know, to the ____ of both the consumers and the providers of information.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I think this the first time that the ____ has done something almost totally against student interest.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has made ____ arrangements to control the number of demonstrators on the streets.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not ____ the level of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "From the quality of the writing I can only ____ that someone helped him. His work is usually nowhere near as good.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has taken the ____ decision to consult the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Is this a ____ picture by Picasso or is it a fake?", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The purpose of the study is to examine the hypothesis that ____ life is more stressful than rural life.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no magic ____ for getting better in English, but lots of reading is an easy and enjoyable way to improve.", "Opt_1": "formula", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The human ear has a very ____ structure.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has made ____ any progress towards reducing environmental pollution.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to ____ about the government's decision to raise the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Strauss said his health started to ____ and he was placed on the transplant recipient waiting list.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Biological processes interact strongly with ____ and chemical processes to create the planetary environment.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people say that there should be ____ schools for students who are not so interested in writing or learning from books.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We ____ the right to refuse alcohol service to anyone who cannot provide proper identification.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The result of such ____ was increased poverty in Russia and lost belief in the fairness of governmental institutions.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He has the ____ to be a professional soccer player. He is only 11 but he is already better than anyone else in the school.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I can survive on a ____ income. I don't need lots of money.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and ____ gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This illustrates the variety of ____ choices that a criminal would make in the decision to commit a crime.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The pictures presented aspects of the objects they could not ____ from the equations alone.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Iraq is ____ in a state of civil war.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The teacher gave me a ____ about the need to be in class on time with all my materials.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from power ____ failure, but this is not a concern for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Two thirds of the ____ of the earth are covered with water.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government wants to encourage young mothers in poor areas to ____ parenting classes.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is slightly down from the 19 percent failure ____ last year but still significantly above the failure ____ in other freshmen subjects.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "But the mice did not ____ thorough cognitive testing, which requires intact mobility to navigate various mazes.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The scientists that constitute the ____ all work in the field of cancer research.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ultimate ____ in the country is the President.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To test for a ____ sentence, see if it can stand alone and still mean something.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When a ____ minimum has been found using limits, the limits should then be removed if possible, in order to perform or re-perform the error.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids transmit ____ better than air.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ that more nuclear weapons lead to a safe world is irrational.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If the student is determined to be independent of their parents, the student must be a ____ of Indiana since at least December 31 of the previous year.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Once Windows Movie Maker has opened, you will need to ____ the video clip that you would like to edit.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The university has decided to ____ its modern languages department to meet the growing interest.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When you employ an electrician to do a job in your house, you hope they will be ____ at their job.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In western countries most people ____ at the age of 65.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is not always possible to distinguish a ____ of a conflict from a consequence of that conflict.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you ____ your calculator like that, you'll break it.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Knowledge about hazards plays a central but curious ____ in risk perception.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has little chance of success in its ____ to reduce crime unless it creates more jobs.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The OCC provides ____ and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She is going to ____ the course unless there is a drastic improvement in her efforts.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is inevitable that any complex ____ will have some sort of taxation system.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will generate much debate in the classroom, mainly ____ graduate students.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His behaviour has not been very ____ since he returned from vacation.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but ____ language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The time when Hitler was leader of Germany is possibly the most terrible ____ in all of history.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He is an American ____ which obviously puts him in a different category from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government looks likely to succeed in its ____ to reduce child poverty by the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She began to ____ that being overlooked by her supervisor was not a temporary problem.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The two procedures consistently showed that garlic did not inhibit the ____ of oral bacteria.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These tests represent your last chance to ____ what you have learned in the course.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In history class this year, we will ____ the French and Russian revolutions.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For republicans since Cicero there can be no liberty without law, and no ____ law or legal system when liberty is disregarded.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In most modern car factories robots ____ the larger parts.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In proof of this, we may note that slavery did not ____ immediately on the reception of Christianity.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I ____ to put all of my lecture notes online because I do want students to attend the lectures.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A major ____ in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She is yet to ____ basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The drugs are used to enhance performance artificially to the ____ that they give athletes a competitive edge.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company has decided to ____ much time and effort into marketing its new product.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The purpose of this study is to investigate the ____ that men are better in mathematics than women.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The students ____ that I promised to show a DVD on in class today, but I cannot remember doing so.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A doctor will usually ask her patient many questions in order to make a ____ of the illness.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Victims of terrorist attacks are usually given ____ by the government.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very ____ that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at prior to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These documents have an ____ stamp, but I'm not convinced they are authentic.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There are very few people living today who were born ____ to the first world war.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right mixture of ____ that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "California's medical schools and major teaching hospitals are directly and ____ responsible for more than 200000 full-time jobs.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The administration is planning to ____ the school day until 4pm.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He was a soldier, and doubtless felt that it was not his ____ to volunteer advice to the political department.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you can ____ your intelligence with hard work, you have a good chance of success.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The first ____ of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to analyze and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "role", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "job or function", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to ____ changes on the earth beneath them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between learning your first language and learning a second one.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The committee was asked to ____ a report listing the reasons in favour of invading Iraq.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The main ____ of these wars is the social unrest, and the increasing economic and social divergence between the groups of the community.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company's financial ____ has been greatly affected by the rising cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school faces a real ____ in educating students from poor backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You have not made a clear enough ____ between the causes and effects of the disaster.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If your parents want to take you out of school during term time, they must have a ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is especially important to remember that parents as a group have not usually taken the riding lessons and are not competent to ____ their children.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an annual security report detailing statistics ____ crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an external tax expert to ____ its finance methods.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you are unable to attend a class for any reason, and would prefer to work directly from the student guide, please ____ the Training Coordinator.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The purpose of the study is to examine the hypothesis that ____ life is more stressful than rural life.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They have other business interests to which they ____ their attention, and they may be expected to continue to do so.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Beethoven was not an ideal parent and enormous ____ developed between the two, contributing to his son's attempted suicide in 1826.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}]]